// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity",
    answer: "Keep your surroundings clean",
    options: [
      "Waste food",
      "Keep your surroundings clean",
       "Don't use dustbin",
      "Biting your fingernails"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity",
    answer: "Keep your things well organised",
    options: [
      "Keep your things well organised",
      "Not drinking enough water",
       "skimping on sleep",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity",
    answer: "Use a dustbin",
    options: [
      "Split on read",
      "Use a dustbin",
       "Wear dirty clothes",
      "Eating too much sodium food"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity",
    answer: "Never waste food and water",
    options: ["Waste food and water",
      "Eating late at night",
       "Never waste food and water",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity.",
    answer: "Trim your nails",
    options: [
      "Biting your fingernails",
      "Not exercising",
       "Not Sleeping enough",
      "Trim your nails"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity.",
    answer: "Drink lots of water",
    options: [
      "Drink lots of water",
      "Waste water",
       "Not drinking enough water",
      "None"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity",
    answer: "Brush your teeth twice a day",
    options: [
      "Don't brush your teeth at night",
      "Skimping on sleep",
       "Brush your teeth twice a day",
      "Cooking everything in olive oil"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity",
    answer: "Exercise daily",
    options: [
      "Looking at screen right before bed",
      "Exercise daily",
       "Don't your meditation early",
      "Walk up too late"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity",
    answer: "Eat healthy food",
    options: [
      "Eat fast food",
      "Sleep after food",
       "Smoking",
      "Eat healthy food"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "Select the person hygiene and fitness related activity",
    answer: "Early to bed",
    options: [
      "Early to bed",
      "Skimping on Sleep",
       "Not Drinking enough water",
      "None"
    ]
  },
];